♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[Red, in English] Kill me now.
[in English] Kill me now!
[Dmitri, in English] You're not worth it.
- [gunshots]
- [groans]
[gunshots]
- [gunshots]
- [Janine, indistinct]
[sobbing]
[in English] Dad!
- Audrey, run away!
- [in English] No!
[in English] I'm not leaving you
and my daughter, Dad! No!
[sobs]
She's not really your daughter.
[gasps]
[in English] Resting for focus,
focus! I'm right here!
[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
PREVIOUSLY
‪[clanging and clattering]
Is it okay if you go to my school?
- Because Tatoy might not be there yet.
- [buzzing]
[Olga] Um, why… Why is that?
Our moving-up ceremony is near.
Where is my real child?!
I'll never tell you, even if you shoot me.
[gasping]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
Stop it, Red!
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
- [groans and screams]
- [in English] Dad!
[echoing]
[Atoy] We won't be able
to get out anymore.
We'll rot here.
Just think of the people who love you.
No one cares about me now.
[Atoy] My life has no meaning anymore.
[in English] Mission status.
[in English] Outside the establishment.
[in English] Potential headquarters
of Anthony "Atoy" Padua.
[Lily] Even if you say
you don't have a family,
surely, you left a mark
on at least one person.
[huffing]
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
- Hey, guys!
- [exclaims]
Papa Uno, my night is complete
because I saw you. You're so handsome!
- [chuckles]
- [group giggles]
Hi, Papa Uno. I mean, Uno.
Maybe you'd like to join us,
only if you can.
Because Brother Kurt has free pares.
- Yes.
- If you can, Papa Uno.
[Denden] Oh, no, T-Bak looks possessed.
Are you okay?
He's just hungry!
Papa Uno, what do you say?
Come with us.
- Hmm, okay. Okay, let's go.
- [Jona] Oh, no!
- You agreed?
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- There! He agreed.
- [Karla] Wait a minute.
Maybe we're bothering Uno.
- No, not at all!
- [T-Bak] Hey.
[indistinct chattering]
Bothering me? No way!
Actually, I'm really hungry too.
- Oh, there you go!
- Let's go! I'll join you.
- Where is it? Let's go.
- [lively chatter]
So, what are you doing here at the shop?
- Here? Uh…
- [Karla] Yes.
I came to have a suit made.
They told me
this is really the best place.
- You know?
- [muttering]
- Great tailoring, so…
- [overlapping chatter]
So I came here.
Yes, that's it.
But too bad, Brother Atoy isn't here.
No one can take your measurements.
Exactly.
I noticed that too.
I noticed he's not there.
But anyway.
Maybe I'll just borrow instead.
Hmm. What's that?
What did you put in your pocket?
- Huh? Hey.
- Are you hiding something?
- What are you hiding? Show us!
- [overlapping chatter]
They say you're hiding something.
[Jona] What's that? Show us.
[Mona] Let us see.
Show us what you're hiding.
- There is. There really is.
- Ahh!
- [Jona] Hey.
- Wait. Yes. There is, there is.
- Oh no! Surprise!
- What's that? What's that?
No, honestly, this is really for Karla.
- Wow!
- I really want to give this to you.
- [Jona] For Karla? Oh, what--
- Karla, this is for you.
- [exclaiming]
- [sneaky music playing]
Oh my! You're lucky you're cute!
I can tolerate you. Me, as if?!
[muttering]
Oh my. I can't stand my hunger anymore!
- Let's go!
- Exactly!
- [lively chattering]
Let's go, Papa. Papa Uno.
[indistinct chattering]
- [music fades]
- [door clicks open]
[sinister music playing]
Boss.
Audrey and Janine have already left.
How?
Your son brought them.
[music intensifies]
[line rings]
Gav, are you with Audrey? Go home now.
[Gavin on the phone] No, Dad.
Tell me the truth first.
[Gavin sobs]
[in English] Did you kill Grandpa?
We'll talk about it when you get home.
[Gavin on the phone] Answer me first, Dad!
Whatever your aunt told you,
it's more complicated than that.
[Gavin on the phone] So, it's true!
How could you do that?!
Your niece, your sister, and then…
Even your own father.
You hurt all of them?
What's next? Me?
[in English] Are you going
to kill me too, Dad?
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
Madam.
[in English] Where's the girl?
Can I sit first?
Uh, oh.
I heard the coffee here is good.
Would you like some, madam? My treat.
[in English] What are you trying to do?
Our deal was that today,
you'll give us back the kid.
Because, madam, she's at home.
But she's with Charmi.
Um…
Honestly, I don't want you
to worry anymore.
And I don't want you
to have problems with the kid,
so, it's okay
if I take care of her instead.
What are you saying?
Uh, maybe…
Maybe, madam, I could…
take care of the child.
Uh, adopt her, like that. [titters]
Can I?
[in English] Of course not.
You need to give her back to me.
But how, madam? Because…
The child already believes I'm her mother.
Can't we just make it real?
You won't have to worry anymore.
No payment, free of charge.
No.
- And don't ask why. Just return the--
- [phone ringing]
[in English] Can you
just stay here, please?
[in English] I-I need to take this call.
[phone blips]
What?
She's about to tell her husband.
It's chaos here. Come home.
They might do something to me.
I can't yet. The child isn't here.
Olga didn't bring her.
Why?
[in English] I don't know.
She wants the kid to herself.
We need the child.
Audrey escaped,
and the child is the only way
to bring Audrey back here,
so she won't speak.
What the hell, hon? How did Audrey escape?
That's not important.
I just-- I just need the kid, okay?
[in English] Fine. I'll see what I can do.
Hurry!
Audrey might do something.
[suspicious music playing]
She already knows Janine isn't her child.
Just think what Atoy will do
when he finds out
Ibyang is really his true child.
[music fades]
Ibyang is Atoy's child?
What did you hear?
Nothing, madam.
Uh--
[in English] Stop right there, Olga.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
We're not done talking.
Uh, you said it, didn't you?
That Atoy is Ibyang's real father?
Then why…
Why don't you tell him the truth?
Why are you hiding it?
[in English] That's none of your business,
and you better keep your mouth shut.
We paid you.
Yes. You paid me to pretend
to be Ibyang's mother.
But not to lie to Atoy.
[in English] What do you want?
More money? How much?
Just to shut your mouth.
- Oh, so--
- Money is all you care about.
Look at you. You talk so big.
Sure, you're rich, you have money,
but your fart stinks too!
We're just the same!
So, if you belittle me,
I'd rather tell Atoy everything.
- [in English] Not so fast!
- Ouch!
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
You're really messing with my hair, huh!
Hey, don't underestimate me!
I'm a fighter too!
You think you're decent people.
Wow, turns out your evil
is on a whole different level.
Good thing I didn't bring Ibyang here!
[Olga scoffs]
Good luck to you,
because I'll tell Atoy everything,
and Atoy will deal with you!
You're not going to do that,
because you're going to surrender
Ibyang to me!
[in English] Make me!
[smirks]
Just a warning, okay.
I'm not only a good actress,
I'm also good at martial arts.
Brown belter here!
[tense music playing]
Ouch! [groans]
So, you think you can scare me?!
- Huh?!
- Ouch!
Your bag may be expensive,
but mine is tougher!
[grunting and groaning]
[pained grunting]
[in English] What the hell
is inside your bag?!
What?! It hurts, doesn't it?
That's what happens
when your bag is full of coins!
[shrieks, coughing]
[in English] Somebody help me!
- [coughs]
- Ma'am, ma'am!
- What happened to you, ma'am?
- [coughs]
[in English] You idiots!
You let her get away!
[security guard] Chase her, chase her!
- [coughs]
- [music fades]
Here, dude. I'm telling you.
[in English] Best pares
in all of Tabang Lupa!
- It's solid. Mmm-hmm.
- [Kurt] Try it.
It's really solid!
It's delicious. It's true!
Mmm. Really delicious.
- [Bunda] Oh.
- Especially the soup, Brother Kurt.
Mmm, so good.
- You're good at eating soup.
- Mmm.
I think it'll taste better if I add this--
Ah, wait! Wait.
- I'll handle that.
- No, I'll do it.
No, hey! I'll handle it.
I can do this.
- Really? Okay then.
- Yes, it spilled.
[Bunda] There. We've got garlic.
- There, it's delicious.
- And this one.
I don't know what it's called. [chuckles]
- [in English] Oh, thank you.
- There.
There. Okay, let's try it.
[in English] Enjoy.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, right? Oh!
- I feel something.
- What?
- You're thirsty.
- [chuckles]
You're good! Mmm-hmm.
I'm good, right?
That's why I also have water for you.
- Wow!
- [Bunda] Mmm-hmm.
- Hey, Bunda!
- Why?
- [in English] Thank you.
- Hey, show some respect.
The person's eating.
He can't eat properly anymore.
Miss Siony, this is my moment!
[Uno] It's okay, Miss Siony.
I'm really okay.
Ah, because, well--
[Uno] Eat now. It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, Karla.
Your stare is quite different.
It's clinging, like body odor!
Crazy!
I saw Uno opening Brother Atoy's gate.
Then he suddenly hid his tool.
[T-Bak] Really? No way?
Yes. Hello?
We don't even know him.
He just suddenly appeared here.
[Karla] Maybe he's Brother Atoy's enemy.
That's why he's here, to take revenge.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [indistinct chattering]
Doesn't seem like it!
You know what? You're just AS!
Always suspicious!
- [scoffs]
- [Indistinct chattering]
- It's delicious, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
[Bunda] More water?
Well, you're the one paying. Right?
[Bunda] What did you say?
- I need banana cue.
- [indistinct chattering]
- Huh?
- [suspicious music playing]
[T-Bak] What are you planning?
[indistinct chattering]
Discount?
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[chuckles] Do you want more?
The egg is delicious, isn't it?
[chuckles]
[music fades]
[Charmi] Don't move!
[rousing music playing]
[gentle music playing]
God…
Charmi!
- [chuckles]
- My God!
- [giggles]
- I got nervous--
What's wrong with you?!
Why do you have a gun?!
What-- What is that?! It's so big!
Oh, no, it's nothing! It's fake, look!
It's wood, see!
[giggles]
You scared me.
It's fake! I asked for it
from the production designer
who's courting me, Egay!
[Charmi] Oh, it's nice, look!
Effective for scaring people.
[giggles]
- [Charmi] Oh.
- Hey.
[in English] Thank you.
You watched over Ibyang.
Where is she anyway?
Oh, well.
After eating, she went upstairs.
I checked the room.
She's been asleep for a while.
Hey! What did Madam Martina say?
Did she agree
that you'll be Ibyang's official mother?
- [melancholic music playing]
- Mmm.
Look at this.
We look so cute here.
Like real mother and child, right?
Oh, yes. So cute!
You know, just when I really started
to love that child,
that's when I found out the truth
about her parents.
Huh?
You know the real--
Ibyang's real parents?!
[music fades]
It's Atoy.
[sentimental music playing]
[in English] For real?!
It's Atoy? Wait, that's crazy.
Wait.
Atoy is Ibyang's real father?!
That's why, even though
I want to care for Ibyang
and stand firm that I'll be her mother,
of course, that wouldn't
be right, would it?
I still need to give her back
to her real parent.
To Atoy.
[music fades]
It's my fault.
Even Emerson got dragged into this.
[sighs]
Never mind. Tomorrow,
I'll look for another place to stay.
So Atoy won't get mad at me.
It's embarrassing.
Paldo, come on.
You know Atoy.
If he were here,
he'd be the first
to offer his house to you.
Miss Cita.
[clicks tongue] Emerson
once mentioned something to me.
About…
Atoy's other job.
Isn't his mission finished yet?
Maybe.
Ame, has Atoy called or texted you?
[pensive music playing]
Just recently.
Even if he's very busy,
he always leaves instructions
here at the shop.
This is the longest time
he hasn't sent word while on a mission.
Oh.
Paldo, better rest now.
Stay in Atoy's room while he's away.
Emerson is on his way here.
He's just taking care of things
over at his burned shop.
- Ah, okay, Miss Cita.
- [Cita] All right.
Knock, knock.
Uno. Uh…
Good evening.
Do you need something?
Uh, sorry.
I came here late.
But I'd like to have a suit made.
I really need it.
Oh, sorry. Atoy isn't here.
But if you want,
I can take your measurements instead.
- Oh, is that okay?
- Yes, yes.
You write it down.
Okay, okay.
Thank you. But is it okay if
I use the restroom?
[Uno] If it's okay.
Ah, oh sure, there.
Go inside, there.
[Cita] Then straight ahead.
- Here?
- [Cita] Yes, yes. That door.
- Straight ahead? Ah, okay. All right.
- [Cita] Yes.
[suspicious music playing]
[Paldo] Ah, okay, Miss Cita.
- I'll go upstairs now.
- Ah, okay, okay.
It's better to get
Uno's measurements upstairs.
- Okay.
- Come on.
[Cita sighs]
[music fades]
Ah, Brother Kurt.
[Denden] Oh, Karla.
Any news about Emerson?
Does he still have his things?
I don't know.
[sneaky music playing]
Wait.
Where are they?
They ate and ran.
Here, I packed your leftovers.
Thanks.
Hmm.
[in English] Karla, what took you so long?
- [in English] Where have you been?
- Here, I bought banana cue.
For all of us.
- Oh, take some.
- Oh.
[both, in English] Thank you.
[Kurt] Okay, thank you.
One fell.
- [Kurt and Denden] Cheers.
- Oh.
[indistinct chattering]
So, where's Uno?
I knew it. You like Uno too, huh?
- You're just playing coy!
- Huh?
- [giggles]
- [in English] Ah, Karla, just admit it.
[in English] All the girls here
have a crush on him.
- And T-Bak said you do too.
- Really?
Psst, that's just T-Bak.
Don't believe her!
- [in English] Okay, okay, okay.
- Give me the banana cue!
Actually, if you're looking for him,
he went to Atoy's shop.
Because Ame and Miss Cita are still there.
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
[phone keypad beeping]
- [line ringing]
- [music intensifies]
Sir, I found the room.
But there's a problem.
I don't know the access code.
Do you know the combinations?
[music fades]
All right.
Okay, I'll try it.
[tense music playing]
[device blipping]
[Ibyang] Tatoy?
Tatoy?
Yoo-hoo!
[pensive music playing]
Ibyang? Ibyang?
Ibyang?
Tatoy.
I know
that you're struggling,
and surely you're hungry.
[melancholic music playing]
But don't ever think that you're alone.
[Atoy] I could die here
and it would be over.
Don't say that!
Now is the time to apply
what you taught me before.
And don't let negative thoughts
get all tangled up in your mind.
Like thread
through a needle.
It passes but doesn't stop.
[Atoy] I have no family.
My life has no meaning anymore.
All the people who love you
and care for you,
they are your family!
And I'm here too, Tatoy.
You'll know me soon.
So, don't give up, okay?
[Atoy] What are you saying?
Just have faith.
And don't lose hope.
Okay, Tatoy?
Tatoy.
- Tatoy!
- [faded voice] Atoy…
[Lily] Atoy.
- [gasps]
- [music fades]
[gasps softly]
[Lily] Atoy.
You must be dreaming.
You were talking earlier.
[gasping]
[somber music playing]
It was Ibyang.
[pants]
I dreamt of Ibyang.
She was talking to me.
You're right, Ibyang.
I shouldn't think that no one…
no one cares about me.
- [panting]
- [melodramatic music playing]
You're right.
We need to escape from here.
[groans]
We need to get out.
[Lily] I want that, but…
How will we do it?
- [music fades]
- [Atoy panting]
[rousing music playing]
Boss, the police are outside.
They're looking for you.
[somber music playing]
What did they say?
Has someone reported us?
No, boss.
[in English] Good.
Boss, what if Audrey
went to another police station?
[ominous music playing]
I already tipped off
the precincts we control.
If anyone reports there, I'll be informed.
[Mongki] What about your dad, boss?
[smirks]
That's easy.
I'll talk to the police myself.
If Audrey didn't go there directly,
there's only one person they'll go to.
[music fades]
[Roger] Who, boss?
[tense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Do you think
that we would not find out?
[in English] Do you know this woman?
[in English] Don't tell me
that you don't know them.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] You say you have no family.
Don't drag them into this.
[in English] You know I met this
Audrey before?
[Samir, in English] Hello, Ms. Audrey.
[in English] She's a beautiful woman,
isn't she?
[in English] I think even Mr. Dmitri
wanted her to be with me.
[in English] That Audrey,
she could have felt what a real man is.
[in English] What a waste of a woman
now that she is with you.
[in English] But I will still
make her scream.
[music fades]
[in English] Not in pleasure.
[in English] But I will
make her scream in pain.
- [grunts]
- [music intensifies]
If I find out you hurt them…
I'll stitch you to the wall,
feed you to animals like you.
[in English] I don't even understand
your language, sir.
[in English] Good luck with that.
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
That's Olga's child!
You're in trouble now.
You're a fake daughter.
Why do you say I'm fake?
Olga's child is dead.
[smirks] So, what are you?
A ghost?
- Are you with Ibyang?
- Olga ran away from me.
This night has way too many screw-ups.
[in English] We need that kid.
We're safe here.
How can we be safe, when Daddy isn't here?
- [in English] I'm very, very hungry.
- [groans]
[groaning]
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
UP NEXT
[Atoy, in English] Cufflinks.
We'll use these
in the first stage of our escape.
- We're going to escape.
- ♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias